When we first defined our tables we defined
the relationships in terms of constraints. Now, we
are going to implement that relationship into our
query using a join this join will allow us
to query the weather table for values from
a specific location setting. We'll start by adding a
SQL Ite query builder class variable at the
top of weather provider. We'll initialize the SQLI to
query builder in the static constructor for the
class, describing the join between both tables. Note,
since both tables have a column named _ID.
We must explicitly use the table name in
order to disambiguate which underscore ID we are
talking about in the join. Then we can
define the query. The query is to find
using the question mark replacement syntax. These question marks
will be replaced by the query parameters. Since we
allow people to specify the start date in the URI,
we're also going to add a second selection, which includes
checking to see whether date text is greater than or
equal to our parameter. Next, we'll add a method to
get the weather by location entry, using the same query
builder. Note, that we fetch the parameters from our URI.
And though the string arrays, they can be substituted into
our query. Note that if URI does not contain a start date we actually use
a different selection. Finally, we add the function
into the query routine of our content provider.